http://www.visitingphysicians.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
We, Centene Corporation (Centene), are very aware of the privacy concerns our members and others who visit this web site may have. This statement is intended to explain the types of information Centene may obtain about visitors to our Web Site (the “Site”) and how the information is used.
1. COLLECTED INFORMATION
We collect a limited amount of personal information from you in certain areas of the Centene web site (the “Site”) for various reasons. The following is a description of what information is collected:
Registration Information. Though visitors of our Site do not have to register in order to access information on our Site, certain healthcare providers do have to register in order to access the secure provider section of the Site. This registration process is not done via the Site. Information is collected from providers separately in order to authorize their use of the provider section. Also, there may be third party features of the Site, which could require a separate registration. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party features before providing personally identifiable information. Centene is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.
IP Addresses. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address. In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser and/or type of computer you are using. Centene collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic to the Site, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to maintain and improve the Site. We do not link IP addresses to your personally identifiable information. We can and will use IP addresses, however, to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms & Conditions or to protect our service, the Site, customers or others.
Use of Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that some web sites (including the Site) transfer to an individual’s hard drive for research purposes. Centene uses cookies to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on the Site, and make improvements based on the data we collect. The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of the Site. The Site’s advertisers and other partners may also use cookies in connection with the services and web sites to which the Site links. We do not control these cookies.
2. WHO COLLECTS THIS INFORMATION
Centene collects the information described above via the Site. In the case of third party features such as advertising, co-branded areas or links to other web sites, such third parties may also collect information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third parties before providing personally identifiable information. Centene is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.
3. HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED
Generally, Centene uses registration information to learn more about how visitors use the Site and to measure areas of interest. This allows Centene to build features and functionality that will enhance your Site experience. We might also use this information to provide customer support, enforce our Web Site Terms and Conditions or other similar matters. Aggregate information is also used to help us run and maintain the Site, study traffic patterns and generally learn about the usage of the Site.
Unrelated Companies. Centene occasionally shares limited customer information with companies we hire to provide operational, marketing, or advertising support, companies that help us distribute our products and services, or companies that provide products and services we want to offer. The companies we choose must satisfy our security and privacy requirements. We share your information with these companies only if they agree to treat it confidentially and only if it is legally permissible to do so. We limit the information we provide these companies to what we reasonably believe they “need to know” in connection with their agreement with Centene, and we don’t permit them to use our customer information for any purposes outside our oversight or control.
Government Authorities and Litigation. Sometimes a law, court order, or other judicial or administrative process requires us to provide information to a government authority or party to a private lawsuit. We will provide the information that we in good faith believe is required to comply with the law, order, or other process. We may also have to disclose certain information in court documents if we have to bring an action against you, for example, to collect a debt you owe us.
4. WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED
We will not knowingly disclose or authorize the disclosure of personal identifiable information (other than aggregate statistical information) to any third party without your consent unless (1) we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Web Site Terms and Conditions or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Centene’s rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities or (2) we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
5. LINK TO OTHER SITES
While you are using the Site, you may be linked or directed to other third party web sites outside the Site that are beyond Centene’s control. Each of these third parties may have a privacy policy different from that of Centene. These links and banners may take you to the web sites of advertisers, sponsors and co-branding partners. Centene is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. These other web sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party web sites before providing personally identifiable information.
6. SECURITY PROCEDURES WE USE
Centene has adopted and adheres to security standards to protect non-public personal information against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure. We have developed administrative, physical, and technical barriers to protect the information stored on this Site.
7. CHANGES IN THESE TERMS
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post notices on the Site at the time of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Please contact us if you have questions or concerns regarding Centene’s Privacy Statement.
